Every Story. One Remote.
Meet Netflix Pro.
Make It Personal
A space for everyone.
Find Your Next Story
Featured stories. A world to explore.
Follow Your Mood
Eleven ways into your next watch.
Keep Exploring
Across titles. Between rows. Always in focus.
Go Inside The Story
Discover. Save. Make your choice.
One More Episode
Your seasons. Your next chapter.
Have Something In Mind?
Find it with your remote.
Pick Up Where You Left Off
Continue Watching. My List. Your favourites.
Watch Your Way
Seek, choose a language, settle in.
Your Profile. Your Choice.
Make the experience your own.
Your Next Watch Starts Here
Netflix Pro for Android TV.